Hello everyone, I'm Takahashi Mikujin from Hyugaizaka 46.
I'm Kaho Fujishima.
We are now at New Chitose Airport in Hokkaido!
Yay!
This is New Chitose Airport.
That's because
46 Hours TV is now on the air.
It's a day two
We are here in Hokkaido!
We came to Hokkaido! To do a live broadcast!
Yay!
Thank you very much!
So far, various members have been doing campaigns to put up posters
We have been conducting a campaign to put up posters in various regions
Today, we would like to do the campaign in Hokkaido!
Today we are going to...
Yes!
I'm going to ask a local, Kahorin, to lead the way!
Leave it to me!
I'll lead the way.
Let's do our best!
Let's have fun!
Yes we are now at ESCON Field Hokkaido
This is the Hokkaido Nippon-Ham Fighters.
This is the base of the Hokkaido Nippon-Ham Fighters.
Have you been here before?
It's my first time.
I've always wanted to go.
I'm so happy that my wish came true today.
I'm a little high today.
I'm having so much fun.
I'm so happy.
It's sunny today.
I heard that the roof has been lifted for the first time this season.
There's no roof on today's game.
That's right.
It's a great day to be here, isn't it?
Yes, it was.
We had great weather.
What's going on?
Polly has an announcement to make.
What is it?
Kaho Fujishima, Friday, June 28th.
First Pitch for Escondido Field!
No way!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
I'm so happy! Thank you so much!
I'm so surprised.
I didn't know.
I didn't know! You know, I didn't think it was weird when you were at the vending machine.
Oh, why not?
I just thought maybe you were bringing coffee to the camera right now.
Oh, my God!
That's great! Thank you! Connie!
Oh!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Da-da-da-da-da!
Ha-ha-ha.
Da-da-da-da!
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Ha-ha-ha.
Thank you
Thank you very much.
Yes, I just got back from Escondido?
No, it was a big place.
They moved us to another place.
We've moved.
We're going to start working on the posters.
How's it going?
I've done my research.
Thank you.
The owner is from Miyazaki Prefecture.
The owner is from Miyazaki.
So I thought it would be nice to visit a Miyazaki-related restaurant.
Is this it?
Yes, it is!
Well, let's play rock-paper-scissors for the winner!
Yes, an appointment! It's a real apo!
My first apo norie.
Right, Serious Apo!
The winner goes.
Oshaku, rock, paper, scissors!
I'll go then.
I'll be waiting for you.
I'm nervous.
I'm nervous too.
Please do your best.
I'm a member of an idol group called Hyugaizaka46,
We're currently doing PR activities around the country for our upcoming live performance in Miyazaki Prefecture,
I'd like to film for YouTube here.
Mr. Mikani!
OK.
That's OK.
Let's both go right away.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I'm sorry.
Nice to meet you.
This is the place.
What a nice place! May I?
Thank you very much!
I'll get right on it.
Thank you very much.
Maybe I'll write something about Hokkaido, too.
Great! Can you write in detail in Hokkaido?
Yes, we are very particular.
Wow!
Thank you very much!
We are going to perform at the Sun Marine Stadium in Hyuga in September.
You came to our show for that environment, didn't you?
That's right!
Thank you very much!
Excuse me!
I put up a poster near the sheep's house.
Please take a look when you come by.
Please do!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
It's crunchy.
What's that flavor?
It's our number one seller.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
We'd like to do a street performance somewhere in Sapporo.
Yes, we'll do our best.
We'll do our best.
Good luck!
Okay, well, what should we do?
Well then, we'll do our best, and we'll return you to the studio.
I'll be back at the studio... and I'll see you in Odori Park... with those two hollyhocks... who are related to the same label.
That's right.
I might be able to join you there.
So I was thinking of going to Odori Park.
Is that a good spot for street performances?
Yes, I see a lot of people performing on the street.
I used to watch them when I was working in Hokkaido.
I also shot my first documentary in Odori Park.
So I think I can go back to my roots and sing.
I practiced in the car a while ago, so please go and sing your best.
Mikuni-san taught me.
No, no, no, no, do your best.
Yes, I'll do my best.
I'll be going.
Thank you very much. I'll be going.
Hello.
I'm sorry, it's the year.
Hello, everyone. I'm Mikuni Takahashi from Hyugaizaka 46.
I am Kaho Fujishima from Hyugaizaka 46. I look forward to working with you.
We are currently in Kyushu, of course, but we are also visiting all over the country to promote our 46-hour TV program.
We are here in Sapporo, which is the furthest away from Miyazaki, but we are hoping that people who have relatives in Miyazaki or friends in Miyazaki will come and visit us and tell us about Hyuuga-saka 46.
We thought we would do this street live to see if we could meet people who know about Hyugaizaka 46.
Thank you very much.
So, please give my regards to Puffo!
Today's street live, Mikuni-san, one of my seniors, came to the event,
He said he was a bit nervous about singing alone,
I went to pick up two very reliable Hiiraki members.
Please give them my best regards.
The first song we sang was,
It is called "You cry like a squeaking wheel,
It is a song that holds deep memories for me,
Even if I climb that song someday,
I would be happy if you could listen to it with a gentle feeling as it is a relaxing and gentle song.
What should I say?
To you who are crying that you hate yourself
I can stay in uniform on the rooftop of the school building at sunset
I've only got a few months left
The old train is running on the old rails
Running on old rails
Old wheels on old tracks
The tracks
The next generation is on new rails
Chasing dreams
No matter how far
I know I can run
Thank you
Congratulations
Thank you very much.
Hyuugaizaka46 has a lot of god songs.
That's right.
Among them, there is one that I think
I think they should be known by more people.
I have a sparkling divine song that I think more people should know about.
I asked the two members of Hiragi to make an acoustic version of it
I'd like to send happy feelings to all of you.
The next song will be the last one.
I'm going to sing a song called "Once in a lifetime in summer.
Thank you for watching!
I know you said you were busy with your part-time job.
I was shaken by the anxiety and the cards in your hand
Like a dusk, you appeared and stood
I touch the sun's back, I can't see your face
I love you
me
I felt the distance between us
The once-in-a-lifetime summer is passing
I don't know why my tears are overflowing
The empty sandy beach
the waves that come in and sweep me away
Someone forgot
A straw hat
somewhere far away
Thank you very much
Summer is the theme of this song.
I sang this song on the theme of summer
At the end of this summer
I'm going to be in Miyazaki Prefecture
Miyazaki Prefecture
Hyuga Miyazaki Comprehensive Athletic Factory
At the Hyuga Sun Marine Stadium
At the Park
At the park
at Hyuga Sun Marine Stadium
Hyuga Saka 46
festival!
Hyuga
If you want to make summer memories
or just want to have a youthful time with Hinata and 46
Please come to Hinata Sunmarie Stadium!
We look forward to seeing you there!
Please come to Hyuga Festival!
Please come to the festival!
Excuse me.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for listening
Thank you very much
If you ever want to do it again, please come.
I look forward to working with you again.
I look forward to working with you again in the future.
Thank you very much.
I'll do my best.
Good bye.
Thank you for your hard work.
Here it is.
Rum.
Next is
Tools
tools.
I say larger, don't I?
This is
Soft human skins
The color is amazing!
This is
Edo Deer
Edo Deer is underground in Hokkaido
They are born in Hokkaido.
What do you think?
Bon appétit.
Yes, thank you.
I look forward to it
Delicious.
Is it soft?
It's soft.
Nice and warm but good
My first Genghis Khan
Mmmm
Delicious
I'm glad.
Is it good?
It's pretty chewy.
Yeah, it is.
It's good.
I'm afraid I'm going to have to take a really low-medium curve.
I'm going to eat it.
We've properly put a Potter on this one, too.
One more.
Yes, sir.
Of course, this one.
The PR is worth it, though.
I've just finished all the live broadcasts of the 46-hour TV program.
After eating for two hours, I thought I'd like to go somewhere a little associated with it,
This time, I went to a restaurant that Kumi and I had visited before,
There is a restaurant that Kumi went to,
I heard that there was a restaurant where Kumi and I had a dinner party when Hiragana Keyaki was on tour at ZEPP,
That's right. This was on the first day of 46 Hours TV,
I asked Aya if she had ever eaten Genghis Khan. I asked her if she had ever eaten Genghis Khan,
She said yes,
And she said, "Yes, I have." And she said, "Here?
This one!
- That's where we're going now. I see.
Yes, that's right. I would like to visit a store that has such a connection with you.
It would be nice if we could put up posters here.
Well... ah!
- Wow! Wow! Wow! It smells good.
Smells great, sounds great.
I'll take this... Yes. I heard you're going.
- I'll leave it to you. Good luck!
I'm off! Bye!
Excuse me. Hello. I'm just visiting with the Hinatazaka 46 group.
OK! Yay!
Then let's get to work on the drawing.
I've always wanted to try it.
This is my first time.
Excuse me.
Hello.
Good evening.
Excuse me for interrupting.
Come on in here.
Oh, is it water?
It's Zingisuka.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Izawa bought it.
Please try Genghis Khan when you come to Hokkaido!
Please do.
I'm going to Tanuki Koji shopping street now.
Tanuki Koji is a really long
It's a shopping street, so there are quite a few stores in there.
Wait, there are a lot of people!
Right now, I'm between Tanuki Kouji 4-chome and 5-chome.
And it's Saturday, so there are a lot of people.
Lots of people.
It's very crowded.
It's amazing.
If it was just a souvenir shop..,
It's not only for people living in Hokkaido,
I'm looking for such a shop.
We are looking for such a store.
We want people from all walks of life to see our shop.
That's right.
There are live music clubs.
Some live music clubs, some restaurants...
Oh! Look at the stores! There are many souvenir shops!
Okay, let's start here.
Where is it? The tannery.
Let's take a shot with a tanuki!
A tanuki!
Here's a tanuki!
There are tanuki everywhere because of the tanuki construction.
The second tanuki
This is a tanuki.
Second tanuki
OK, I got it!
OK, I did it!
Let's go draw it.
Is there a Marimo in Tokyo?
Marimo is like that moss?
Yes, it is.
I think they have it.
Yes, they do.
I've never really seen it.
I've never really seen it before, but it's common in souvenir shops in Hokkaido.
Is it famous? Marimo.
Maybe it's pretty famous. I used to grow marimo.
I grew about three of them.
They call them hiki.
Three.
It's so touching to see a bear next to me watching over them.
Like it has long arms and legs.
It's as you would expect.
I put up a poster.
Thank you very much.
I wonder if you put it in a very good place.
The spiral staircase from the first floor to the second floor.
Everyone, when you come to Hokkaido,
Buy some souvenirs at Kanukiya,
and also this poster,
I would be very happy if you could come and see this poster.
Thank you very much.
Sapporo PR campaign is over.
It's over.
How was it? How was the triumphant return to your hometown?
Well, it was a really happy day,
I was able to meet a lot of warm people in the vast land of Hokkaido,
I was very happy to meet so many warm people in the vast land of Hokkaido,
I have a dream to perform in Hokkaido,
I have a dream to perform in Hokkaido.
I would like to make that come true someday,
I would like to make the Hinata Fest a great success for that.
Let's do our best.
Thank you very much for watching.
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.
Thank you for watching.